thqnordic.com 2018-10-04

# Privacy policy | THQ Nordic GmbH

_**General information  
This privacy policy has been translated from German (company is based in Vienna, Austria) to English by Google Translate.**_

## **Privacy Policy**

Thank you for visiting the official website [https://www.thqnordic.com](https://www.thqnordic.com/) (the "website") of THQ Nordic GmbH, which under this privacy policy is also referred to as "THQ Nordic", the "Company", "we" and "Us". This Privacy Policy outlines what kind of information we collect about you and how you can decide how we collect and use that information. This Privacy Policy applies in whole or in part to our subsidiaries and websites of our products.

### Data protection

We have written this privacy policy to explain to you, in accordance with the provisions of the EU General Data Protection Regulation, which information we collect, how we use data and what options you have as a visitor to this website.

Unfortunately, it is in the nature of things that these explanations sound very technical, but we tried to describe the most important things in a simple and clear manner.

### Automatic data storage

When you visit websites nowadays, certain information is automatically created and stored, including on this website.

If you visit our website as it is now, our web server (computer where this website is stored) automatically saves data such as the IP address of your device, the addresses of the visited subpages, details of your browser (eg Chrome, Firefox, Edge, ...) and date and time. We do not use this information and usually do not disclose it, but we can not rule out that it will be seen in the event of unlawful behavior.

### Storage of personal data

Personal data that you submit electronically to us via this website, such as name, e-mail address, address, or other personal information you transmit in the course of submitting a form, or comments in the blog, will be used in connection with time/date of entry and your IP address and only stored for said specified purpose. This information is kept safe and will not be disclosed to third parties.

We use your personal data exclusively for communication with those visitors who expressly request contact and for the handling of the services and products offered on this website. We will not disclose your personal information without consent, but we can not rule out that this information will be seen in the event of unlawful behavior.

If you send us personal information via e-mail - i.e. outside of this website - we can not guarantee secure transmission and protection of your data. We recommend that you never send data by e-mail unencrypted.

### Contact via the website

Due to legal regulations, the website contains information that allows visitors to contact our company quickly and to communicate with us directly, which also includes a general address of the so-called electronic mail (e-mail address). If you contact the data controller (us) via e-mail or through a contact form on our website, the personal data provided by you will be automatically saved. Such personal data, voluntarily transmitted by an individual to the Company, is stored for the purpose of processing or contacting the respective person. There is no disclosure of this personal data to third parties.

### Registration on our website

We offer the option of registering on our website, providing personal data. The personal data transmitted to us can be seen on the respective registration forms. This personal data shall be collected and stored solely for internal use by us and for this specific purpose. The THQ Nordic employee responsible may initiate the transfer to one or more other employees of THQ Nordic, who can in turn use the personal data, again, only for internal use attributable to the purpose of the registration.

By registering on the website, the IP address assigned by the Internet service provider (ISP) of the person submitting the data is stored, along with the date and time of registration. The reason for the storing of this data is to prevent fraudulent use of our services. In case of need, the storage of this data enables us to investigate criminal activities. In this respect, the storage of this data is required to legally protect data processors. Essentially, a disclosure of said data to third parties is not intended, unless there is a legal obligation to share it, or if the data needs to be forwarded as part of a criminal prosecution.

By registering, said voluntarily provided personal data enables the internal data processor to provide the registrant with content or services that, due to the nature of the case, can only be offered to registered users. Registered persons are free to modify the personal data given at registration at any time or to delete it completely from the database of the data processor.

The internal data processor shall, at any time upon request, provide information to each registrant as to which personal data about the registrant is stored. Furthermore, the data processor corrects or deletes personal data at the request or reference of the registrant, insofar as this does not conflict with any statutory storage requirements. All team members of the data processor are available to the registrant as a contact person in this context.

### Data protection in the case of job applications and in the application process

The data processor collects and processes the personal data of job applicants for the purpose of handling the entire application process. The processing can also be done electronically. This is particularly the case if an applicant submits corresponding application documents to the data processor by electronic means, for example via e-mail or via a contact form on the website. If the Company concludes a contract of employment with an applicant, the data transmitted will be stored for the purposes of the employment relationship in accordance with the law. If no contract of employment with the candidate is concluded by the Company, the application documents will be automatically deleted six months after receipt of the application, provided that deletion does not conflict with any other legitimate interests of the Company. Other legitimate interest in this sense, for example, a burden of proof in a procedure under the General Equal Treatment Act (GETA).

### Your rights

In principle, you have the rights to information, correction, deletion, restriction, data portability, revocation and objection. If you believe that the processing of your data violates data protection law or if your data protection claims have otherwise been violated in a way, you can complain to the supervisory authority. In Austria, this is the Data Protection Authority whose websites you can find at https://www.dsb.gv.at/.

### TLS encryption with https

We use https to transfer data securely on the Internet. By using TLS (Transport Layer Security), an encryption protocol for secure data transmission over the Internet, we can ensure the protection of confidential data. You acknowledge the use of this security of data transfer at the small lock symbol in the upper left corner of the browser and the use of the https scheme as part of our Internet address.

### Cookies

Our website uses HTTP cookies to store user-specific data.

A cookie is a short data packet that is exchanged between the web browser and the web server, but is completely immaterial and only becomes meaningful in connection with a web application like an online store, where it stores the content of the virtual shopping cart.

There are two types of cookies: First-party cookies are created by our website, and third-party cookies are created by other websites (e.g. Google Analytics).

There are three categories of cookies: essential cookies to ensure basic functionality of the website, functional cookies to ensure website performance and targeted cookies to improve the user experience.

We use cookies to make our website more user-friendly. Some cookies remain stored on your device until you delete them. They allow us to recognize your browser on your next visit.

If you do not want this, you can set up your browser so that it informs you about the setting of cookies and you allow this only in individual cases.

You can always delete cookies that are already on your computer or disable cookies. The procedure for doing this varies according to browser, it is best to look for the instructions in Google for the term "delete cookies chrome" or "disable cookies chrome" in the case of a Chrome browser or replace the word "chrome" with the browser of your choice, like e.g. Edge, Firefox, Safari etc.

If you generally do not allow us to use cookies, i.e. you disabled them via your browser's settings, some features and pages may not work as expected.

### Newsletter

If you subscribe to our newsletter, you submit the above personal information and give us the right to contact you via email. We use the data stored in the registration for the newsletter exclusively for our newsletter and do not pass this on to third parties.

If you unsubscribe from the newsletter - you will find the link in each newsletter at the bottom - then we delete all data that was saved with the registration for the newsletter.

### Google Maps Privacy Policy

We use Google Maps from Google Inc. (1600 Amphitheater Parkway Mountain View, CA 94043, USA) on our website.

By using the features of this card, data will be transmitted to Google. What kind of data Google collects and how it uses this information can be found at <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>.

### Google Analytics Privacy Policy

We use Google Analytics from Google Inc. (1600 Amphitheater Parkway Mountain View, CA 94043, USA) to statistically analyze visitor data. Google Analytics uses targeted cookies.

For more information about Terms of Use and Privacy, please visit <https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html> or <https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en>.

#### Pseudonymization

Our ambition in accordance with the GDPR, is the improvement of our offerings and our web appearance. As the privacy of our users is of utmost important to us, the user data is pseudonymized. The data processing takes place on the basis of the legal regulations of the § 96 paragraph 3 Telecommunications Act, as well as article 6 of the EU-GDPR paragraph 1 section a) (consent) and / or section f) (legitimate interest) of the GDPR.

#### Deactivation of data collection by Google Analytics

Certain  **browser add-ons to disable** Google Analytic's JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, dc.js) allows site visitors to prevent Google Analytics from using their data.

You may prevent the collection by Google of the data generated by the cookie and related to your use of the website as well as the processing of this data by Google by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available under the following link: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>.

#### Google Analytics addendum to data processing

We have entered into a direct customer agreement with Google for the use of Google Analytics by accepting the "Data Processing Supplement" in Google Analytics.

To read more about the Google Analytics Add-on, please visit [https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/3379636?hl=en&utm_id=ad](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/3379636?hl=en&utm_id=ad)

#### Google Analytics IP anonymization

We have implemented the IP address anonymization of Google Analytics on this website. This feature has been developed by Google to enable that site to comply with applicable privacy practices and recommendations of local data protection authorities when they prohibit storage of the full IP address. The anonymization or masking of the IP takes place as soon as the IP addresses arrive in the Google Analytics data collection network and before the data is stored or processed.

More information about IP anonymization can be found at <https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2763052?hl=en>.

### Google Fonts Privacy Policy

We use Google Fonts from Google Inc. (1600 Amphitheater Parkway Mountain View, CA 94043, USA) on our website. Google Fonts are used without authentication and no cookies are sent to the Google Fonts API. If you have an account with Google, none of your Google Account information will be transmitted to Google while using Google Fonts. Google only records the use of CSS and the fonts used and stores this data securely. More about these and other questions can be found at <https://developers.google.com/fonts/faq>.

What data Google collects and how it uses this information can be found at <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>.

### Google reCAPTCHA

We use Google reCAPTCHA from Google Inc. (1600 Amphitheater Parkway Mountain View, CA 94043, USA) to prevent spam.  
The legal basis for use is Article 6 (1) f (lawfulness of processing), as there is a legitimate interest in protecting this website from bots and spam.

reCAPTCHA is a free service that protects websites against spam and abuse. It uses advanced risk analysis techniques to keep people and bots apart. With the new API, a significant number of your valid human users will pass the reCAPTCHA challenge without having to solve a CAPTCHA. We use reCAPTCHA to secure forms.

By using reCAPTCHA, data will be transmitted to Google using Google to determine whether the visitor is human or spam. To see what data Google collects and what this data is used for, visit <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>.  
Google's Terms of Service and Products can be found at [https://policies.google.com/terms?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en).

### Embedded social media elements

We integrate elements of social media services on our website to display pictures, videos and texts.  
By visiting pages representing these elements, data is transferred from your browser to the respective social media service and stored there. We do not have access to this data.  
The following links lead you to the pages of the respective social media services where it is explained how they deal with your data:

  * Instagram Privacy Policy: https://help.instagram.com/519522125107875
  * For YouTube, the Google Privacy Policy applies: <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>    
  * Facebook Data Policy: https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy    
  * Twitter Privacy Policy: https://twitter.com/privacy

### Facebook Privacy Policy

We use functions of Facebook, a social media network of FIrma Facebook Ireland Ltd., 4 Grand Canal Square, Grand Canal Harbor, Dublin 2 Ireland.

What features (social plug-ins) Facebook provides can be found at <https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/>.

By visiting our website information can be transmitted to Facebook. If you have a Facebook account, Facebook can associate that information with your personal account. If you do not want that, please log out of Facebook.

The privacy policy, which information Facebook collects and how they use them can be found at <https://www.facebook.com/policy.php>.

It is also possible to block Facebook social plugins with add-ons for your browser, for example with the "Facebook Blocker".

### YouTube Privacy Policy

We use YouTube's video service, YouTube, LLC, 901 Cherry Ave., San Bruno, CA 94066, USA.

By accessing pages of our website that have integrated YouTube videos, data is transmitted to YouTube, stored and evaluated.

If you have a YouTube account and you're signed in, it will be associated with your personal account and the data stored in it.

What data Google collects and how it uses this information can be found at <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>.

### Twitter Privacy Policy

We use features on this website from Twitter, a Twitter International Company social network, One Cumberland Place, Fenian Street, Dublin 2 D02 AX07, Ireland.

This also allows personal data to be transmitted to Twitter. We do not monitor this data exchange and do not store anything about it.

If you would like to know more about the use of your data by Twitter, you will find all the information in the Twitter Privacy Policy at <https://twitter.com/privacy>.

If you have an account on Twitter, you can change your privacy settings in Account Settings at <https://twitter.com/settings/account>.

### Google+ Privacy Policy

We use features on Google+ from Google+, the social network of Google Inc. (1600 Amphitheater Parkway Mountain View, CA 94043, USA).

If you want to take full advantage of the features offered, you'll need a Google Account.

Even when using the functions (Google +1 Buttons, Google+ Badge, Follow button, Google+ Share button and Link, Sign-In Button, Hangout Button) without Google Account information is already sent to Google.

If you're signed in with your Google Account while using the features listed above, your data can be published worldwide (depending on your settings: <https://plus.google.com/settings/>), and Google collects and evaluates it, as appropriate.

What data Google collects and how it uses this information can be found at <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>.

### Instagram Privacy Policy

We use social networking site Instagram features by Instagram LLC, 1601 Willow Rd, Menlo Park CA 94025, USA.

We can display images and videos with Embed Embed Instagram features.

By calling up pages that use such functions, data (IP address, browser data, date and time, cookies) are transmitted to Instagram, stored and evaluated.

If you have an Instagram account and you're signed in, that information will be associated with your personal account and the data stored in it.

The privacy policy, which information Instagram collects and how it uses it can be found at <https://help.instagram.com/155833707900388>.

### LinkedIn Privacy Policy

We use Social Media Network features on LinkedIn, LinkedIn Corporation, 2029 Stierlin Court, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA.

By visiting sites that use such functions, data (IP address, browser data, date and time, cookies) are transmitted to LinkedIn, stored and evaluated.

If you have a LinkedIn account and you are logged in, it will be associated with your personal account and the data stored in it.

The privacy policy, which information LinkedIn collects and how it uses it can be found at <https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy>.

### Pinterest Privacy Policy

We use buttons and widgets on our site from the social media network Pinterest, Pinterest Inc., 808 Brannan Street, San Francisco, CA 94103, USA.

By calling up pages that use such functions, data (IP address, browser data, date and time, cookies) are transmitted to Pinterest, stored and evaluated.

The privacy policy, which information Pinterest collects and how it uses it can be found at <https://policy.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy>.

### Facebook Pixel Privacy Policy

On our website we utilize the Facebook Pixel of Facebook, a social media network of the company Facebook Ireland Ltd., 4 Grand Canal Square, Grand Canal Harbor, Dublin 2 Ireland.

The code implemented on this website can evaluate the behavior of visitors who have come to this website via a Facebook ad. This can be used to improve Facebook ads and this information is collected and stored by Facebook. The collected data is not visible to us but can only be used within the scope of booking advertisements. The use of the Facebook pixel code also sets cookies.

By using the Facebook Pixel, the visit of our website is communicated to Facebook, so that visitors get to see matching ads on Facebook. If you have a Facebook account and are logged in, the visit to this website will be associated with your individual Facebook user account.

How to use the Facebook pixel for advertising campaigns is available at <https://www.facebook.com/business/learn/facebook-ads-pixel>.

You can change your ad settings on Facebook at <https://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/?entry_product=ad_settings_screen> if you're signed in to Facebook. At <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/preferencemanagement/>, you can manage your preferences for usage-based online advertising. You can disable or enable many providers at once or make settings for individual providers.

More information about Facebook's data policy can be found at <https://www.facebook.com/policy.php>.

### Questions and complaints

If you have any questions or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us by e-mail at office@thqnordic.com.

**Contact**  
THQ Nordic GmbH  
Landstrasser Hauptstrasse 1/2/23  
1030 Vienna  
Austria

Tel .: +43 (0) 1 2365487-0  
Fax: +43 (0) 1 253 30 33 9960  
E-Mail: office@thqnordic.com

Source: Created with the privacy generator of firmenwebseiten.at as well as in parts by the privacy policy generator of DGD Deutsche Gesellschaft für Datenschutz GmbH, which acts as external data protection officer Frankfurt am Main, in cooperation with the Cologne Privacy lawyer Christian Solmecke.
